<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="what_can_do_in_meeting">What can do in meeting?</string>
    <string name="you_will_find_the_settings_tab_within_the_main_panel_or_the_meeting_menu_bar_after_clicking_settings_you_will_have_the_subsequent_options_audio_click_settings_on_your_pc_or_mac_client_to_check_your_audio_or_during_a_video_meeting_click_settings_within_the_menu_bar_to_activate_toggle_for_then_click_on_the_audio_tab_to_check_your_audio_settings_select_the_microphone_sink_and_check_out_a_special_audio_source_if_the_opposite_side_can_hear_you_select_the_speaker_dropdown_and_check_out_a_difference_speaker_source_if_you_will_hear_the_opposite_side_video_to_check_your_video_camera_before_or_during_a_video_tab_to_check_your_video_selection_here_you_will_also_click_on_the_sink_arrow_to_modify_between_cameras_that_you_simply_have_connected_to_your_computer_general_you_will_select_additional_preferences_feedback_we_welcome_any_questions_comments_or_feedback_recording_here_you_will_browse_open_your_stored_recordings_all_recordings_are_stored_on_your_local_device_computer_account_here_you_will_upgrade_your_account_to_pro_user_or_manage_your_account_details_learn_more_about_account">You will find the Settings tab within the main panel or the meeting menu bar. After clicking Settings, you will have the subsequent options: Audio: Click Settings on your PC or Mac client to check your audio, or during a video meeting, click settings within the menu bar (to activate Toggle for). Then click on the Audio tab to check your audio settings. Select the microphone sink and check out a special audio source if the opposite side can hear you. Select the speaker dropdown and check out a difference speaker source if you will hear the opposite side. Video: to check your video camera. Before or during a video tab to check your video selection. Here you will also click on the sink arrow to modify between cameras that you simply have connected to your computer. General: you will select additional preferences Feedback: We welcome any questions, comments, or feedback Recording: Here you will browse/open your stored recordings (all recordings are stored on your local device/computer). Account: Here you will upgrade your account to pro user or, manage your account details (Learn more about Account).</string>
    <string name="zoom_lets_you_record_your_web_conferencing_calls_as_videos_a_handy_feature_for_sharing_the_meeting_with_people_who_may_have_missed_it_or_for_reviewing_what_was_said_when_you_record_you_must_choose_whether_to_use_the_local_or_cloud_options_local_means_you_store_the_video_file_yourself_whether_locally_on_your_computer_or_in_another_storage_space_that_you_provide_with_cloud_which_is_for_paying_members_only_zoom_stores_the_video_for_you_in_its_cloud_storage_different_account_types_come_with_different_amounts_of_storage_one_convivence_of_the_cloud_option_is_that_people_can_stream_the_video_in_a_web_browser_once_it_is_ready">Zoom lets you record your web conferencing calls as videos, a handy feature for sharing the meeting with people who may have missed it or for reviewing what was said. When you record, you must choose whether to use the local or cloud options. Local means you store the video file yourself, whether locally on your computer or in another storage space that you provide. With cloud, which is for paying members only, zoom stores the video for you in its cloud storage (different account types come with different amounts of storage). One convivence of the cloud option is that people can stream the video in a web browser once it is ready.</string>
    <string name="record_the_video_call">Record the Video Call: -</string>
    <string name="once_you_have_started_or_joined_a_meeting_you_can_perform_the_following_actions_from_the_menu_bar_located_at_the_bottom_of_the_meeting_window_move_your_mouse_to_toggle_you_can_invite_more_people_to_join_by_email_im_sms_or_meeting_id_screen_share_your_desktop_or_specific_application_window_group_or_private_chat_participants_and_chat_mute_unmute_audio_stop_start_video_configure_your_settings_your_settings_leave_or_end_the_video">Once you have started or joined a meeting, you can perform the following actions from the menu bar located at the bottom of the meeting window (move your mouse to toggle). You Can invite more people to join by email, IM, SMS or meeting id. Screen share your desktop or specific application window. Group or private chat. Participants and chat. Mute/Unmute Audio. Stop /Start video. Configure your settings your settings. Leave or end the video.</string>
    <string name="before_you_start_meeting">Before You Start Meeting</string>
    <string name="record_the_video_calls">Record the Video Calls</string>
    <string name="what_can_do_in_zoom_meeting">What can do in Zoom Meeting</string>
</resources>